Guide to the Georg Kreisel Papers SC0136
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Georg Kreisel papers
1957-1984
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kreisel, Georg
SC0136
24.75 Linear Feet
Correspondence with professional colleagues, collaborators, students, and others, primarily from 1962 to 1984, lecture notes, manuscripts and other writings.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of Logic and the Foundations of Mathematics at Stanford University. Born in Graz, Austria, Kreisel received his B.A. degree in 1944 and his M.A. degree in 1947, both from Cambridge University. He served at Lecturer in Mathematics at the University of Reading from 1949 to 1954, 1957 to 1958 and 1959 to 1960. He was a member of the Institute for Advanced Study at Princeton from 1955 to 1957, and Professor of Mathematics at the University of Paris from 1960 to 1964. He first came to Stanford University in 1958 as a Visiting Associate Professor of Mathematics and later as Visiting Professor of Logic and Mathematics. Since 1964, he has held a joint appointment in Stanford's departments of Mathematics and Philosophy. In 1966, he was elected a Fellow of the Royal Society. Kreisel died on March 1, 2015.
Description of the Collection
Correspondence with professional colleagues, collaborators, students, and others, primarily from 1962 to 1984, lecture notes, manuscripts and other writings.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Mathematics -- Philosophy.; Logic, Symbolic and Mathematical.; Kreisel, Georg; Kreisel, Georg; Kreisel, Georg; Stanford University. Department of Mathematics; Stanford University. Department of Philosophy
- Correspondence
  - A- misc. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Apt, Krystof R. – [Polish Institute for Mathematics] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - B – misc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barendregt, H. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Barendregt, H. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barwise, Jon (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Barwise, Jon (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barwise, Jon (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beeson, Michael (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Beeson, Michael (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Berlin, Isaiah (Box 2, Folder 2a)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bishop, Erret (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Block (Box 2, Folder 6a)
  - Boffa, M. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Browder, Felix E. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bullard, Sir Edward (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - C – misc. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cassels, J. W. S. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cagnoni, D. (Box 3, Folder 4a)
  - Cellucci, Carlo (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cleave, John P. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Paul (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cordeschi (Box 3, Folder 8a)
  - Crick, Francis and Odile (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - D – misc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DeHorney (Box 3, Folder 10a)
  - de Jongh, Richard (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Derrick (Box 3, Folder 11a)
  - Dreben, Burton (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Duchin, Peter (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - E – misc. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eggenberger (Box 3, Folder 14a)
  - Erdos, R. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Engeler, Erwin (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ershov, Y.L. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - F – misc. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Feferman, Sol (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Felscher, Walter (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fenstad, Erik (Box 3, Folder 20a)
  - Franzen, T. (Box 3, Folder 20b)
  - Friedman, Harvey (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Friedman, Harvey (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - G – misc. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gabbay, Dov M. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Gandy, Ro. O. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Geach, Peter (Box 4, Folder 3a)
  - Gerber, Harvey (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Grandy, Richard E. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Girard, J-Y (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Girard, J-Y (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Glass, A. M. W. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Godemont (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gondard (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Goodman, Nicholas (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Graham, R. L. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Grilliot, T. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Guaspari, David (Box 5, Folder 5a)
  - Guillaume (Box 5, Folder 5b)
  - H – misc. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hajek, P.; Hanf, W. P. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Halmos (Box 5, Folder 7a)
  - Halpern, J. D. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Harrington, L. (Box 5, Folder 8a)
  - Heyting, A. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Howard, William (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Howard, William (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Howard, William (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Howard, William (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Howard, William (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Howard, William (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Howard, William (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Howard, William (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Howard, William (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Howard, William (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Howard, William (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hubner (Box 7, Folder 4a)
  - Hyland, M. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - I, J. – misc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Jack, T. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jacobson, Nathan (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Jeroslow, Robert G. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Jeroslow, Robert G. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jockusch, Carl (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jockusch, Carl (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Joel (Box 8, Folder 7a)
  - Jung, Joachin (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - K – misc. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Karp, Carol (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Keisler, J. H. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Kripke, S. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kleene, S. C. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - L – misc. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lachlan, Alistair (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lacombe, D. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Leivant, Daniel (Box 9, Folder 2a)
  - Lerman, M. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lerner, Manny (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Levy Azriel (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lieberherr, Karl (Box 9, Folder 5a)
  - Lifschitz (Volodya) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Littlewood (Box 9, Folder 6a)
  - Lob, M. H. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lopez-Escobar, E. G. K. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lopez-Escobar, E. G. K. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lorenzen, P. – Festschrift (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lowe, William L. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Luckhardt, Horst (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - M – misc. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - MacIntyre (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Maclane, S. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - “Madmen” – Guberman (Box 9, Folder 14a)
  - Magari, Roberto (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Makowsky, J. A. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Marek, W. [Polish Institute of Mathematics] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Martin-Lof, P. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Martin-Lof, P. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mathematical Review (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mints, G. E. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mints, G. E. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mints, G. E. (Box 10, Folder 8a)
  - Monk, L. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Muller, G. H. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Murdoch, Iris (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mycielski, Jan (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Edward (Box 11, Folder 2a)
  - Nerode, Anil (Box 11, Folder 2b)
  - 0 – misc. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - P – misc. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Pappinghaus, P. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Parikh, R. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Parsons, Charles (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Platek, R. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Porte, Jean (Box 11, Folder 8a)
  - Pohler, W. (Box 11, Folder 8b)
  - Posy, Carl (Box 11, Folder 8c)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Prawitz, Dag (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Putnam, Hilary (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Queneau, R. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - R – misc. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rabin, M. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Radu, E. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rautenberg, Wolfgang (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ressayre, J. P. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Richardson, Daniel (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Reinhardt (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Abraham (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Julia (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, H. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Royal Society – Brouwer obituary (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Royal Society – correspondence (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Bertrand (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - S – misc. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Saarinen (Box 13, Folder 7a)
  - Sabbagh, G. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sabbagh, G. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Sacks, G. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sacks, G. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Sacks, G. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Sacks, G. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sacks, G. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Sanchis, Luis Elpidio (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Scarpellini, Bruno (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Schaeffer (Box 14, Folder 6a)
  - Schutte, Kurt (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Schutte – Festschrift (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Schwichtenberg, Helmut (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Scott, Dana (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Scott, Dana (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Scott, Dana (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Serre (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Shepherdson, J. C. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Shockley, Wm. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Shoenfield, J. R. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Shore, Richard A. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Simpson, S. G. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Slisenko, Anatole (Box 16, Folder 5a)
  - Smorynski, Craig (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Smorynski, Craig (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Smorynski, Craig (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Soare, Robert (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Solovay, Robert M. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Spector, Clifford (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Statman, Richard (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Statman, Richard (Box 17, Folder 5a)
  - Statman, Richard (Box 17, Folder 5b)
  - Stavi, Jonathan (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Steel, John (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Stegmuller, W. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Surma (Box 17, Folder 9a)
  - Swart, H. de (Box 17, Folder 9b)
  - T – misc. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Tait, Ww. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Tait, W. W. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Takeuti, Gaisi (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Thom, M. Rene (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Thompson, David B. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tosi (Box 19, Folder 6a)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Troelstra, A. S. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Tselishchev (Box 21, Folder 2a)
  - Ullman, Arthur (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Unique (Box 21, Folder 3a)
  - V – misc. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - van Heijenoort, Jean (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Vesley, R. E. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Ville (Box 21, Folder 6a)
  - Vladik, B. F. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Vogel, H. (Box 21, Folder 7a)
  - W – misc. (includes Ian Williams) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Wang, Hao (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Weingartner, Paul (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Wigner, Eugene (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Winternitz, Robert (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Yasugi (Box 21, Folder 12a)
  - Yates, Michael (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Yourgrau, Wolfgang (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ziman, J. M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Zucker, J. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Addison, 1977 Oct - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Armendariz, 1977 Aug (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ashton, 1977 Jan- 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Barendregt, 1977 Apr - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Barwise, 1977 May - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Beeson, 1977 May (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Bernays, 1977 May - 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Block, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Bokser, 1977 Jul - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Buchholz, 1977 Jun - 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cagnoni, 1977 Apr - 1977 Sep (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cappelletti, 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Case, 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Cellucci, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Crick, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Dehornoy, 1977 May - 1977 Jun (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - del Franco, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Drogalin, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Dummett, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Dyson, 1978 Jan - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Engeler, 1977 May - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Ershov, 1977 Dec - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Faust, 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Felscher, 1977 Apr - 1977 Dec (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Fensted, 1977 Dec (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Fried, 1977 Nov - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Friedman, Harvey (including paper 'The Intuitionistic Completeness of Intuitionistic Logic Under Tarskian Semantics"), 1977 Apr - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Friedman, Sy, 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Gabbay, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Geach, 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Girard, 1977 Jun (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Glymour, 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Godel (correspondence regarding his death), 1978 Jan - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Guillaume, 1977 Apr - 1977 Dec (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Haller, 1977 Dec - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Harrington, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Homer, 1977 Dec - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Hubner (including paper by Kreisel, "On Wittgenstein's Conversations About the Foundations of Mathematics"(In German and English), 1977 Feb - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Hyland, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Jarvie, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Jockusch, 1977 May - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Kim, 1977 Dec (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Kleene, 1977 Apr - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Kochen, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Kopliansky, 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Kuiper, 1977 Jan - Sep (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Lam, 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Leivant, 1977 May (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Lerman, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Lifschitz, 1977 Dec - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Lin, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1977 Dec (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Lorenzen (including paper by Kreisel, "Formal Rules and Questions of Justifying Mathematical Practice"), 1977 Apr - 1978 Apr (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Luckhardt, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - "Madmen", 1977 Mar - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Marcus, 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Mcintyre, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Mints, 1977 Mar - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Monk, 1977 Sep (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Murdoch, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Muser, 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Nelson, 1977 Feb - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Nerode, 1977 Dec - 1978 Jan (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Neston, 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Owings, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Pappinghaus, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Parikh, 1977 May - Oct (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Paris, 1977 Apr - May (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Perzanowski, 1976 Dec - 1977 Oct (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Pohlers, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Popovic, 1977 Dec - 1978 Mar (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Prawitz, 1978 Jan - Mar (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Putnam, 1977 Nov (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Quine, 1977 Oct - 1977 Nov (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Radu, 1977 Sep (Box 28, Folder 1A)
  - Robin, 1977 Oct - 1977 Dec (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, 1977 Aug - 1977 Dec (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Royal Society, 1977 Aug - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Saarinen, 1977 Apr - 1977 Nov (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Sabbagh, 1977 Jul - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sacks, 1977 May - 1977 Nov (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Schlipf, 1977 May - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Schmerl, 1977 Nov - 1978 Jan (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Schuler, 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Schutte, 1977 Nov (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 11A)
  - Scott, 1977 Jun - 1978 Jan (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Shapiro, 1977 Oct (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Shepherdson, 1977 Jun - Aug (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Shimony, 1978 Jan - Mar (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Shoenfield, 1977 May (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sieg, 1977 Mar - Dec (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Silver, 1977 Oct - Nov (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Simpson, 1977 Oct - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Sinaceur, 1978 Jan (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Slisenko, 1977 Apr - Oct (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Smorynski, 1977 Apr - Oct (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Snapper, 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Solovay, 1977 Dec - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Speck, 1976 Sep - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Specker, 1977 Oct - Dec (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Statman, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Stavi, 1977 May - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Stegmuller, 1977 Sep - Nov (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Suppes, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Swinnerton-Dyer, 1977 Oct - Nov (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Takeuti, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Troelstra, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Van Heijenoort, 1977 May - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Vogel, 1977 Dec (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Weingarten, 1976 Sep - 1978 Feb (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Yasugi, 1977 Apr - Aug (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Yates, 1977 Apr - 1978 Jan (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Zucker, 1977 Apr - 1978 Mar (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Dittos (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Memos (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Lecture: "Successes and Limitations of Mathematization" given at WCP Meeting in Dusseldorf (also Includes correspondence with Bochenski Regarding Lecture), 1978 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Addison, 1978 May - Sep (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Agazzi, 1978 Aug (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Barendregt, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Barwise, 1978 Apr - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Beaker, 1979 Jan - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Benacerraf, 1978 Jun - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Birch, 1978 Jul - Oct (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Blair, 1978 Dec (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Borga, 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Bouveresse, 1978 Apr (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Buchholz, 1978 Apr (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Cagnoni, 1978 Jul - Sep (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Cellucci, 1978 Apr - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Chomsky, 1979 Feb (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Christodoulidis, 1978 Oct - Nov (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Conceptus, 1978 Mar - Nov (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran, 1978 Mar - Oct (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Crick, 1978 Mar - 1979 Apr (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - del Franco, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Deligne, 1978 Mar - 1979 Feb (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Engeler, 1978 Apr - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Ershov, 1978 Sep (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Faust, 1978 Sep (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Feferman, 1978 Jul - 1979 Mar (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Felscher, 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Ferebee, 1978 Nov (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Floistad, 1977 Nov - 1979 Apr (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Fried, 1977 Oct - 1978 Jun (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Friedman, 1978 May - 1979 Jun (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Gauthier, 1978 Oct - 1979 Jan (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Girard, 1978 Sep (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Glushkov, 1978 Sep - 1979 Jan (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Goad, 1978 Mar - 1979 Jun (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Grabiak, 1978 May - Jun (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Griffor, 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Guillaume, 1978 Mar - Apr (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Hajek, 1978 Nov (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Haller, 1978 May - Sep (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Harrington, 1978 Apr (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Hawkins, 1978 May - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Herre, 1978 Jun - 1979 Feb (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Howard, 1978 Jul - 1979 Mar (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Hubner, 1978 Dec - 1979 Feb (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Hyland (including paper, "Referee's Report on the Paper 'Filter Spaces and Continuous Functionals"), 1978 May - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Jervell, 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Jockusch, 1978 Apr - 1979 Feb (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Ketonen, 1978 Mar - Nov (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Kim, 1978 Nov - Dec (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Kochen, 1978 Mar (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Kreinovich, 1979 Jan - Feb (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Kuiper, 1978 Jun - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Kunen, 1978 May - Aug (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Lacon, 1978 Aug (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Lam, 1978 Mar - Nov (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Leinfellner, 1978 Mar - Sep (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Leivant, 1979 Jan (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Le Lionnais, 1978 May (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Lenstra, 1978 Jul - 1979 Jan (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Levy, 1978 May - Nov (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Lieberherr, 1978 May (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Lifschitz, 1978 Mar - Jul (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1979 Jan - Feb (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Lorenz, 1978 Oct - 1979 Jan (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Lucas, 1978 May (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Luckhardt, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - MacIntyre, 1978 Apr - Dec (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Makowsky, 1978 Dec (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Manson, 1978 Nov (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Marek, 1978 May - 1979 Mar (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Mints, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Morley, 1978 Sep (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Motchane, 1978 Jun - 1979 Mar (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Murdoch, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Mycielski, 1978 Oct - 1979 Apr (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Nianias, 1979 Jan (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Okada, 1978 Mar - 1979 Feb (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Parikh, 1978 Jul - 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Perry, 1978 May - Oct (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pohlers, 1978 Apr - Sep (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Ponziani, 1978 Jun - Jul (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Prawitz, 1978 May - Sep (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Previale, 1978 Mar (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Priky, 1978 Oct (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Quine, 1978 Dec (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Rautenberg, 1978 Dec - 1979 Feb (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Reiter, 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Reznikoff, 1979 Jan - Mar (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Ribenboim, 1978 May - 1979 Mar (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Ringot, 1978 Oct - 1979 Jan (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, 1978 May (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Rogers, 1978 Apr - Oct (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Saarinen, 1978 Jan - 1979 Feb (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Sabbagh, 1978 Apr - Oct (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Sachs, 1978 Apr - 1979 Jun (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Schlipf, 1978 Mar (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Schmerl (including paper, "Uber eine mit Hilfe von Reflexionsformeln erzeugte Feinstruktur uber PRA - Erweiterungen"), 1978 Apr (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Schmidt, 1978 Jul - 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1978 Oct - 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Scott, 1978 Mar - 1979 Jan (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Seldin, 1979 Jan - Apr (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Shepherdson, 1978 May - 1979 Jan (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Shimony, 1978 May (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Simpson, 1978 Apr - 1979 Feb (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Smale, 1978 Dec (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Smorynski, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Solovay, 1978 May (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Speck, 1978 Apr - Jun (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Statman, 1978 Mar - 1979 Mar (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Stavi, 1978 Jul - 1978 Nov (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Stevenson, 1978 Mar - Sep (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Stolzenberg, 1978 Apr - 1979 Jun (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Sundholm, 1978 May - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Suppes, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Takeuti, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Termini, 1978 Mar (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, 1978 Jun - Oct (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Troelstra, 1978 Jan - 1979 Jun (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Verena, 1978 Dec - 1979 Jun (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - von Deln, 1978 Aug - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - von Heijenoort, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - von Wright, 1978 Oct - Dec (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Weingartner, 1978 May - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Wette, 1978 Apr (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Wigner, 1978 Aug (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Wojtylak, 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Yasugi, 1978 Mar - Jun (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Yates, 1978 Mar - 1979 May (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Zinoviev, 1978 Nov - 1979 Feb (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Zucker, 1978 Apr - 1979 Apr (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Communications regarding review of Wittgenstein Book: ''Remarks on the Foundations of Mathematics" in "American Scientist'' (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Communications regarding UNESCO meeting on Aristotelian Logic, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Dittos (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Evaluations (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Godel Obituary (Correspondence Regarding) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Letters Regarding Visit to Graz, 1979 Jan - Jun (Box 31, Folder 24)